The frog カエル
A young frog 一匹の若いカエル
An old frog 一匹の年寄りのカエル
ただし、このアもアンもともに、ワン、トゥー、スリーのワンと元は同じ言葉です。
母音の前にはアンの方を使います。
A frog, two frogs. An old frog, three old frogs. A little tadpole, four little tadpoles.
二つ以上のカエルの時、フラグがフラグズになり、
二つ以上のオタマジャクシの時、テッドポールがテッドポールズになります。
意外の名詞の複数は、単数の語尾にズまたはイズの音が加わってできるのです。
B動詞の活用
I am a young frog now. I was once a little tadpole. I shall soon be an old frog.
I am. I was. I shall be.
You are a young frog now. You were once a little tadpole. You will soon be an old frog.
You are. You were. You will be.
He is a young frog now. He was once a little tadpole. He will soon be an old frog.
He is. He was. He will be.
She is a young frog now. She was once a little tadpole. She will soon be an old frog.
She is. She was. She will be.
It is a young frog now. It was once a little tadpole. It will soon be an old frog.
It is. It was. It will be.
We are young frogs now. We were once little tadpoles. We shall soon be old frogs.
We are. We were. We shall be.
You are young frogs now. You were once little tadpoles. You will soon be old frogs.
You are. You were. You will be.
They are young frogs now. They were once little tadpoles. They will soon be old frogs.
They are. They were. They will be.
The verb, which is used when something is something, has a general form of the letter B.
The verb changes its form in relation to the meaning of the subject, the number, or the time it is shown.